

SHARIQUE KHAN UX/UI DESIGNER

8882797433, 8707725542 sharique12khan@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

-Working as a Creative designer (UX/UI), having 8 years of experience., Web, Mobile Application, & User Interface Design, Branding, Visual & Creative Graphics, Digital, Marketing Videos making. Currently working at Goeventz, Gurgaon.

Has ability to solve all sorts of design challenges with creativity, Efficiency and precision. Ability to frame ideas into graphics With excellent knowledge and Experience of designing.

Has excellent hands on Art, designing Web Pages in Adobe XD, Photoshop, Specialise in Graphics Web and mobile UI, Creating Requirement.

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

- UX/UI Design
- Wireframe Designing
- Interactive Prototypes
- · Card Sorting
- Mockup Design
- Banner, Animated banner
- Marketing Promotional Video
- Web & Print Material Design
- Android/iOS Mobile Design

TOOLS

- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Fiama
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effect
- Adobe Premiere Pro

WORK HISTORY

Present Media Pvt. Ltd.

SR UX/UI DESIGNER JUNE 2020 TO TILL

UX/UI Design, Mobile Application, Wire-framing, Interactive Design, Prototyping, Social Media Advertising

WORK HISTORY

Goeventz

SR CREATIVE DESIGNER
JULY 2015 TO APRIL 2020

UX/UI Design, Mobile Application, Wire-framing, Interactive Design, Prototyping, Social Media Advertising, Facebook Ad & Video, Video Making, Re-marketing, Carousal Ads, Website Banner, Offer Banners, Gif

Rj Corp Healthcare Vertical Cryobanks

CREATIVE DESIGNER
OCT 2013 TO 15 JULY 2015

– UI Design, Website, Landing Page, Mockup Design, Brochures, Catalogue, Print ad, Newspaper ad, Magazine ad, Sticker, Hoarding, Banner and other printed materials for them.

GFB-Great Foods & Beverage Pvt. Ltd.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER FEB 2012 TO OCT 2013

-Working on UI , Video Making, Laminate, Packaging Re-marketing, Magazine Ads, Website Banner, all POP Design.

PORTFOLIO LINK

https://www.coroflot.com/sharique/uxdesign

PERSONAL DETAIL

Date of Birth: February 17th 1987

Marital Status : Married

Father's Name: (Late) Md. Ahmad Khan

Nationality : Indian

EDUCATION

UX UI Dedign Adobe After Effect (2018) One Year Advance Diploma in Multimedia From Zed Career Academy. B A (2007) Dr. R. M. L. University, Faizabad(UP)

Mohd Sharique Khan